<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>privacy on blog.dataparty</title>
    <link>https://blog.dataparty.xyz/tags/privacy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in privacy on blog.dataparty</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2022, Weru and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.dataparty.xyz/tags/privacy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DEFCON 31 - Snoop unto them, as they snoop unto us</title>
      <link>https://blog.dataparty.xyz/blog/snoop-unto-them/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dataparty.xyz/blog/snoop-unto-them/</guid>
      <description>The official videos from DEFCON 31 have been posted!
Below you can watch our talk &amp;ldquo;Snoop unto them as they snoop unto you&amp;rdquo;. The talk, slides, files and code are also available for download.
 Follow and Support If you enjoyed our talk, please consder following:
 Buy us a coffee - https://ko-fi.com/dataparty Get rfparty - https://rfparty.xyz Mastodon - https://partyon.xyz/@dataparty Instagram - https://www.instagram.com/datapartydao Twitter - https://twitter.com/datapartydao Join our discord https://discord.gg/JrYQ3f4Pxz  Mailing List #mc_embed_signup{clear:left; font:14px Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; max-width: 75%; } /* Add your own Mailchimp form style overrides in your site stylesheet or in this style block.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re speaking at DEFCON 31</title>
      <link>https://blog.dataparty.xyz/blog/defcon-or-bust/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dataparty.xyz/blog/defcon-or-bust/</guid>
      <description>We are excited to announce that we have been invited to speak at DEFCON 31 this August! Now that we&amp;rsquo;re accepted, we need your help getting there!
We need to raise $5,000 over the next 6 weeks to bring all of our team members to the conference and to make all of the demos picture perfect.
Please consider buying us a coffee or becoming a monthly supporter. You&amp;rsquo;ll also get access to our private Discord Server by becoming a member.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of Party</title>
      <link>https://blog.dataparty.xyz/blog/state-of-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dataparty.xyz/blog/state-of-party/</guid>
      <description>Today billions of people lead double lives. One, grounded in their physical existance. And another, contained within the harddrives of countless corporate clouds. Lifetime&amp;rsquo;s of content and metadata are being shoveled into networks hostile to free expression and privacy.
Your data is destined to be stored on servers you do not own. To be crunched and combed over for corporate gain, government survailence and exploited by cyber criminals for ill gotten profits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WTF is a KDF? </title>
      <link>https://blog.dataparty.xyz/blog/wtf-is-a-kdf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dataparty.xyz/blog/wtf-is-a-kdf/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this week a letter from an activist imprisoned in France was posted to the internet. Contained within Ivan Alococo’s dispatch from the Villepinte prison was a startling revelation. Police had cracked his LUKS hard drive password. A feat that once was impossible can now be accomplished in a few months by harnessing as many as 10,000 servers with modern GPUs. At the root of this breach is a cryptographic function that is showing its age, PBKDF2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rfparty - a new way to see BLE</title>
      <link>https://blog.dataparty.xyz/blog/rfparty-a-new-way-to-see-ble/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.dataparty.xyz/blog/rfparty-a-new-way-to-see-ble/</guid>
      <description>Today, Millions of IoT devices emit wireless BLE advertisements.
Rfparty is an app for exploring your wireless world. Built for educators, developers, cybersecurity specialist and the privacy minded to audit these BLE signals.
Is BLE Private? BLE has become a major part of many people&amp;rsquo;s digital experience, but are these devices built with reasonable privacy in mind? Today there is no way for consumers to know for sure, other than to read the media- and if recent headlines are a barometer, the state of BLE privacy is rather questionable.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
